<resources>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_UP_KEY">Up: Moves to the previous file, folder or menu item.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_DOWN_KEY">Down: Moves to the next file, folder or menu item.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_LEFT_KEY">Left: Moves to the parent folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_RIGHT_KEY">Right: Opens the current folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_OK_KEY">OK: Plays the current file or folder, or executes the current menu item.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_CANCEL_KEY">Cancel: Press quickly to cancel the current function or clear selection of a selected file. Hold for 2 seconds to delete the current file or folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_MENU_KEY">Menu: Opens the File Manager menu.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_DEL_KEY">Review: Reads the name of the current item. Hold for 2 seconds to open the File Info dialog.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_ONE_KEY">Number 1: Moves to the top of the file or folder list. From the menu, pressing 1 executes "copy".</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_TWO_KEY">Number 2: Jumpts to the file or folder list. If you are viewing folders, pressing 2 jumps to the first available file. If you are viewing files, pressing 2 jumps to the first available folder. From the menu, pressing 2 activates the cut function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_THREE_KEY">Number 3: moves up 25 items. From the menu, activates the Paste function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_FOUR_KEY">Number 4: Reads the previous character in the current file or folder name. From the menu, activates the Delete function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_FIVE_KEY">Number 5: Reads the current character\'s military alphabet equivalent. Press twice to hear both the character and the phonetic equivalent. From the menu, activates the Rename function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_SIX_KEY">Number 6: Reads the next character of the current file or folder name. From the menu, activates the New Folder function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_SEVEN_KEY">Number 7: Moves to the bottom of the list. From the menu, activates the Zip function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EIGHT_KEY">Number 8: Opens the go To file dialog.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_NINE_KEY">Number 9: moves down 25 items.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_ZERO_KEY">Number 0: Toggles Selection and de-selection. Hold for 2 seconds to cycle between selection modes: Select All, Select to bottom, Select to Top and Start Continuous Selection.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_NUM_KEY">Pound: Jumps to the root. Hold for 2 seconds to lock and unlock the numeric keypad. In an edit window, press to switch keyboard input modes.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_VOICE_CONTROL_KEY">Hint mode: Voice Control</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_VOICE_CONTROL_UP_KEY">Hint mode: Voice Control Up</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_VOICE_CONTROL_DOWN_KEY">Hint mode: Voice Control Down</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_STAR_KEY">Hint mode: Star key</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_RECORD_KEY">Hint mode: Record key</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_UP_KEY">Up: Moves to the previous item.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_DOWN_KEY">Down: Moves to the next item.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_LEFT_KEY">Left: Moves to the parent folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_RIGHT_KEY">Right: Opens the current folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_OK_KEY">OK: Plays the current file or folder. Hold for more than 2 seconds to invoke the Sleep Timer.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_CANCEL_KEY">Cancel: Exits Explorer and returns to playback. Hold for 2 seconds to delete the current file or folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_DEL_KEY">Review: Repeats the name of the current file or folder. Hold for 2 seconds to open the File information dialog.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_ONE_KEY">Number 1: Moves to the top of the list.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_TWO_KEY">Number 2: Jumpts to the file or folder list. If you are viewing folders, pressing 2 jumps to the first available file. If you are viewing files, pressing 2 jumps to the first available folder.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_THREE_KEY">Number 3: Moves up 25 items from the current position.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_FOUR_KEY">Number 4: Reads the previous character in the file or folder name.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_FIVE_KEY">Number 5: Reads the current character in the file or folder name. Press twice to hear both the military phonetic and the current character.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_SIX_KEY">Number 6: Reads the next character in the file or folder name.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_SEVEN_KEY">Number 7: Moves to the bottom of the list. From the menu, activates the Zip function.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_EIGHT_KEY">Number 8: Opens the Go To File dialog.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_NINE_KEY">Number 9: moves down 25 items from current position.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_ZERO_KEY">Number 0: Toggles Selection and de-selection. Hold for 2 seconds to cycle between selection modes: Select All, Select to bottom, Select to Top and Start Continuous Selection.</string>
  <string name="IDS_HINT_MODE_EXPLORER_MODE_NUM_KEY">Pound: Jumps to the root. Hold for 2 seconds to lock and unlock the numeric keypad. In an edit window, press to switch keyboard input modes.</string>
</resources>
